TIAMO IDZENGA

ZAANDAM · 06 20 32 24 70 tiamo@idzenga.dev · https://idzenga.dev

Good software should be reliable, safe and manageable. In my role as a Cloud (DevOps) Engineer I contribute to the development process, manage build, test and deployment pipelines & cloud infrastructure, document code and monitor applications.

I have experience automating business processes; integrating systems; developing web applications and developing and managing (REST) API's. I also have experience designing and managing architecture for complex systems in the cloud.

EXPERIENCE

SEPTEMBER 2020 – CURRENT CLOUD ENGINEER, A&A CAPACITY

Automating business processes, integrating systems & developing and managing web applications and API's for a diverse group of (enterprise) clients. Work is done within the Microsoft ecosystem, using .NET and cloud services from Azure (Integration Services). I am also responsible for the DevOps side of systems and processes where I manage pipelines and cloud infrastructure.

FEBRUARI 2021 – JULY 2021

GRADUATION INTERN, A&A CAPACITY

Writing a bachelor thesis on system integrations in the cloud. I did research into how system integrations function both on-premises as well as in the cloud and developed a framework using .NET that allows developers to develop modular, manageable system integrations in the cloud.

JULY 2019 – JANUARY 2020

WEB DEVELOPER, CREATIVE SKILLS

Developing custom made web applications, CMS and packages for clients in the e-commerce sector, working primarily with PHP Laravel, Backpack and PostgreSQL/MySQL.

FEBRUARY 2019 – JULY 2019

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN, COPERNICUS INTERCHANGE TECHNOLOGY

I was responsible for developing a full web application on my own with PHP Laravel and MySQL. This application was part of a national (trial) population screening of kidney disease, with the application researchers could maintain the status of patients and their results.

My contribution ensured that thousands of people in The Netherlands were diagnosed with kidney disease in a timely manner, preventing expensive dialysis treatment.

Read more (Dutch): https://copernicus.nl/cases/niercheck/

MAY 2018 - OCTOBER 2018

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, GIN MASTERNODE PLATFORM

From the beginning I was closely involved in this cryptocurrency start-up. Together with the founders we developed a strategy, made a functional design and launched an MVP using Docker, Express for Node.js, Angular, MongoDB and PostgreSQL on the market within a month. Over the next few months we grew to thousands of customers with monthly subscriptions.

Alongside that, I was owner of a shared community of over 500 people of shared cryptocurrency investments where I managed deposits & withdrawals with my own back-end system written in Node.js.

I also wrote on a bi-weekly report where I reviewed various cryptocurrencies to be added to the platform on technical criteria.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, HOGESCHOOL INHOLLAND

My chosen minors were Cloud Computing & ICT Security and User Experience Design & Big Data/Artificial Intelligence.

Finished with bachelor thesis: "Modulaire systeemintegratieoplossingen in de cloud" (Modular system integration solutions in the cloud).

2009 - 2016

VWO, ZAANLANDS LYCEUM

NT-NG profile with subjects: Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry, Biology and Computer Science.

Finished with research project: "De Vleugel" (The Wing), a study into aerodynamics.

SKILLS

- Cloud Computing
- DevOps
- Web & API Development
- Process Automation
- System Integration

- Communication
- Writing
- Critical Thinking

CERTIFICATIONS

• Microsoft Certified: Azure Developer Associate (AZ-204)

ACTIVITIES

At the moment I am following an Azure certification path to specialize further in the direction of DevOps Engineer / Solutions Architect. The next certifications on the track are DevOps Engineer Expert (AZ-400) and Solutions Architect Expert (AZ-304).

Alongside that I am learning about (Web) design using Figma by following several Udemy courses. I plan to launch a portfolio website at https://idzenga.dev.